Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Clark, Hall and Peck, 1890s-1982; Series II
  - New Haven
    - Folded abstracts of title
      - 29-31 - 29-106 (Box 1131)
      - 29-107 - 29-175 (Box 1132)
      - 29-176 - 29-255 (Box 1133)
      - 29-256 - 29-330 (Box 1134)
      - 29-331 - 29-424 (Box 1135)
      - 29-425 - 29-490, 30-1 - 30-43 (Box 1136)
      - 30-44 - 30-113 (Box 1137)
      - 30-114 - 30-185 (Box 1138)
      - 30-186 - 30-239 (Box 1139)
      - 30-240 - 30-297 (Box 1140)
      - 30-298 - 30-370 (Box 1141)
      - 30- 371 - 30-433 (Box 1142)
      - 31-1 - 31-17, 32-1 - 32-44 (Box 1143)
      - 32-45 - 32-107 (Box 1144)
      - 32-108 - 32-189 (Box 1145)
      - 32-190 - 32-260 (Box 1146)
      - 32-261 - 32-346 (Box 1147)
      - 32-347 - 32-431 (Box 1148)
      - 32-432 - 32-460, 33-1 - 33-50 (Box 1149)
      - 33-51 - 33-110 (Box 1150)
      - 33-111 - 33-163 (Box 1151)
      - 33-164 - 33-172, 35-1 - 35-79 (Box 1152)
      - 35-80 - 35-116, 36-1 - 36-29 (Box 1153)
      - 36-30 - 36-95 (Box 1154)
      - 36-96 - 36-165 (Box 1155)
      - 36-166 - 36-265 (Box 1156)
      - 36-266 - 36-332 (Box 1157)
      - 37-1 - 37-67 (Box 1158)
      - 37-68 - 37-150 (Box 1159)
      - 37-151 - 37-241 (Box 1160)
      - 37-242 - 37-259, 38-1 - 38-75 (Box 1161)
      - 38-76 - 38-170 (Box 1162)
      - 38-171 - 38-275 (Box 1163)
      - 38-276 - 38-391 (Box 1164)
      - 38-392 - 38-495 (Box 1165)
      - 38-496 - 38-508, 39-1 - 39-75 (Box 1166)
      - 39-76 - 39-175 (Box 1167)
      - 39-176 - 39-285 (Box 1168)
      - 39-286 - 39-430 (Box 1169)
      - 39-431 - 39-546 (Box 1170)
      - 40-1 - 40-80 (Box 1171)
      - 40-81 - 40-185 (Box 1172)
      - 40-186 - 40-296 (Box 1173)
      - 40-297 - 40-337, 41-1 - 41-35 (Box 1174)
      - 41-36 - 41-110 (Box 1175)
      - 41-111 - 41-225 (Box 1176)
      - 41-226 - 41-330 (Box 1177)
      - 41-331 - 41-454 (Box 1178)
      - 41-455 - 41-554 (Box 1179)
      - 41-555 - 41-618, 42-1 - 42-20 (Box 1180)
      - 42-21 - 42-109 (Box 1181)
      - 42-110 - 42-135, 43-1 - 43-55 (Box 1182)
      - 43-56 - 43-146 (Box 1183)
      - Annex 1-1 - Annex 1-88 (Box 1184)
      - Annex 1-89 - Annex 1-172 (Box 1185)
      - Annex 1-173 - Annex 1-267 (Box 1186)
      - Annex 1-268 - Annex 1-374 (Box 1187)
      - Annex 1-375 - Annex 1-482 (Box 1188)
      - Annex 2-1 - Annex 2-75 (Box 1189)
      - Annex 2-76 - Annex 2-159 (Box 1190)
      - Annex 2-160 - Annex 2-241 (Box 1191)
      - Annex 2-242 - Annex 2-316 (Box 1192)
      - Annex 2-317 - Annex 2-380 (Box 1193)
      - Annex 2-381 - Annex 2-482 (Box 1194)
      - Annex 2-483 - Annex 2-605 (Box 1195)
      - Annex 2-606 - Annex 2-735 (Box 1196)
      - Annex 3-1 - Annex 3-75 (Box 1197)
      - Annex 3-76 - Annex 3-159 (Box 1198)
      - Annex 3-160 - Annex 3-265 (Box 1199)
      - Annex 3-266 - Annex 3-373 (Box 1200)
      - Annex 3-374 - Annex 3-477 (Box 1201)
      - Annex 3-478 - Annex 3-584 (Box 1202)
      - Annex 3-585 - Annex 3-695 (Box 1203)
      - Annex 3-696 - Annex 3-809 (Box 1204)
      - Annex 3-810 - Annex 3-918 (Box 1205)
      - Annex 3-919 - Annex 3-1060 (Box 1206)
      - Annex 3-1061 - Annex 3-1137, Annex 4-1 -Annex 4-25 (Box 1207)
      - Annex 4-26 - Annex 4-80 (Box 1208)
      - Annex 4-81 - Annex 4-165 (Box 1209)
      - Annex 4-166 - Annex 4-245 (Box 1210)
      - Annex 4-246 - Annex 4-337 (Box 1211)
      - Annex 4-338 - Annex 4-430 (Box 1212)
      - Annex 4-431 - Annex 4-530 (Box 1213)
      - Annex 4-531 - Annex 4-633 (Box 1214)
      - Annex 4-634 - Annex 4-754 (Box 1215)
      - Annex 4-755 - Annex 4-831, Annex 1 - Annex 88 (Box 1216)
      - Annex 29 - Annex 155 (Box 1217)
      - Annex 156 - Annex 252 (Box 1218)
      - Annex 253 - Annex 355 (Box 1219)
      - Annex 356 - Annex 381 (Box 1220)
      - Westville 1 - Westville 100 (Box 1221)
      - Westville 101 - Westville 170 (Box 1222)
      - Westville 171 - Westville 240 (Box 1223)
      - Westville 241 - Westville 315 (Box 1224)
      - Westville 316 - Westville 390 (Box 1225)
      - Westville 391 - Westville 480 (Box 1226)
      - Westville 481 - Westville 565 (Box 1227)
      - Westville 566 - Westville 650 (Box 1228)
      - Westville 651 - Westville 740 (Box 1229)
      - Westville 741 - Westville 828 (Box 1230)
      - Westville 829 - Westville 950 (Box 1231)
      - Westville 951 - Westville 1053 (Box 1232)
      - Westville 1054 - Westville 1130 (Box 1233)
      - Westville 1131 - Westville 1230 (Box 1234)
      - Westville 1231 - Westville 1310 (Box 1235)
      - Westville 1311 - Westville 1394 (Box 1236)
      - Westville 1395 - Westville 1490 (Box 1237)
      - Westville 1491 - Westville 1565 (Box 1238)
      - Westville 1566 - Westville 1659 (Box 1239)
      - Westville 1660 - Westville 1765 (Box 1240)
      - Westville 1766 - Westville 1875 (Box 1241)
      - Westville 1876 - Westville 1955 (Box 1242)
      - Westville 1956 - Westville 2069 (Box 1243)
      - Westville 2070 - Westville 2199 (Box 1244)
      - Westville 2200 - Westville 2340 (Box 1245)
      - Westville 2341 - Westville 2490 (Box 1246)
      - Westville 2491 - Westville 2615 (Box 1247)
      - Westville 2616 - Westville 2734 (Box 1248)
      - Westville 2735 - Westville 2895 (Box 1249)
      - Westville 2896 - Westville 2979 (Box 1250)
      - Westville 2980 - Westville 3059 (Box 1251)
      - Westville 3060 - Westville 3141 (Box 1252)
      - Westville 3142 - Westville 3233 (Box 1253)
      - District A (1-47) (Hamden-New Haven line) (Box 1253A)
    - Flat files (numerical)
      - 1-140, 1-141, 2-71, 2-328, 3-235, 3-310, 4-61 (Box 1254)
      - 4-106, 4-445, 5-51 (Box 1255)
      - 5-51 Supplemental (Box 1256)
      - 5-76, 5-78 (Box 1257)
      - 5-374, 6-504, 7-75, 7-207 (Box 1258)
      - 7-468, 9-17, 9-313 (Box 1259)
      - 9-315, 9-317, 10-123 (Box 1260)
      - 12-109, 13-340, 14-476, 14-479, 16-93 (Box 1261)
      - 17-7, 17-45, 17-105 (Box 1262)
      - 18-278, 19-166 (Box 1263)
      - 18-361, 18-458, 19-8 (Box 1264)
      - 19-60, 19-63, 19-68 (Box 1265)
      - 19-73, 19-109, 19-157, 19-163 (Box 1266)
      - 19-187 (Box 1267)
      - 19-187 (continued) (Box 1268)
      - 19-187A, 19-188, 19-199, 19-226 (Box 1269)
      - 19-227, 19-231, 19-238, 19-239 (Box 1270)
      - 19-249, 19-252 (Box 1271)
      - 19-269, 19-297 (Box 1272)
      - 19-304 (Box 1273)
      - 19-304 (continued) (Box 1274)
      - 19-306, 19-308, 19-318 (Box 1275)
      - 20-107 (Box 1276)
      - 20-161, 20-164, 20-189, 20-281 (Box 1277)
      - 20-289, 22-149 (Box 1278)
      - 22-149, 23-9 (Box 1279)
      - 25-33, 25-41, 25-212, 25-519 (Box 1280)
      - 27-251, 27-295, 29-83 (Box 1281)
      - 29-214, 29-239, 29-243, 29-317, 29-357 (Box 1282)
      - 30-51, 30-119, 30-185, 30-228, 30-424, 30-430, 31-6 (Box 1283)
      - 31-9 (Box 1284)
      - 31-13 (Box 1285)
      - 31-13A (Box 1286)
      - 31-13B (Box 1287)
      - 31-13C, 31-13D (Box 1288)
      - 31-13E (Box 1289)
      - 31-13F, 31-13G, 31-14, 31-16 (Box 1290)
      - 32-99, 32-127, 32-138, 32-151 (Box 1291)
      - 32-175, 32-353, 32-411 (Box 1292)
      - 32-417, 32-434 (Box 1293)
      - 32-452, 32-459, 33-5 (Box 1294)
      - 33-16, 33-64, 33-118, 33-122 (Box 1295)
      - 33-145 (Box 1296)
      - 33-167, 33-171 (Box 1297)
      - 35-25, 37-1, 37-59 (Box 1298)
      - 41-323, Annex 1-1, Annex 1-39 (Box 1299)
      - Annex 1-96, Annex 1-230, Annex 1-275 (Box 1300)
      - Annex 2-4, Annex 2-21, Annex 2-22, Annex 2-46, Annex 2-170 (Box 1301)
      - Annex 2-233F, Annex 2-305 (Box 1302)
      - Annex 2-349, Annex 3-23, Annex 3-53, Annex 3-183, Annex 3-431 (Box 1303)
      - Annex 3-1056, Annex 3-1094, Annex 4-2, Annex 4-254 (Box 1304)
      - Annex 4-274, Annex 4-598, Annex 4-765, Annex 4-767, Annex 4-791 (Box 1305)
      - Annex-29, Annex-168 (Box 1306)
      - Annex-246, Annex-279 (Box 1307)
      - Annex-327, Annex-341 (Box 1308)
      - Westville 26, Westville 293, Westville 586 (Box 1309)
      - Westville 761, Westville 888, Westville 899, Westville 902, Westville 1426, Westville 1466 (Box 1310)
      - Westville 1887, Westville 1927, Westville 1966, Westville 1995, Westville 2092 (Box 1311)
      - Westville 2107, Westville 2196, Westville 2199, Westville 2534, Westville 2545, Westville 3032 (Box 1312)
    - Flat files (alphabetical)
      - City of New Haven (grantor-grantee) (Box 1313)
      - DeMarco, Joseph H., railroad property (Box 1313)
      - Long Wharf Development Associates, 1995 (Box 1314)
      - Long Wharf Development Associates Partnership division documents (Volumes 1 -2) (Box 1315)
      - National Box Co. (Box 1316)
      - Oyster grounds (Box 1316)
      - Parcel K-1-B Church Street Redevelopment Area (Box 1317)
      - Stevens New Haven Development Co. (Box 1318)
      - Stevens New Haven Development Co. (continued) (Box 1319)
      - Turtle Bay Condominiums (Box 1320)
      - Whitney Grove Square (Box 1320)
      - Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 1320)
    - Index card file
      - Streets in alphabetical order listing actions taken by New Haven Board of Aldermen and Engineering Dept. (1920s -1960s)
        - A-L, Corca 1920s-1960s (Box 1321)
        - M-Z, Corca 1920s-1960s (Box 1322)
  - Other Connecticut cities and towns
    - New Haven County Atlas, Undated (Box 1323)
      Consists of a torn c. Dolph & Stewart, Map Publishers, New York atlas for locations in Ansonia, Branford, Clinton, Killingworth, Madison and miscellaneous individual maps.
    - Ansonia
      - Index card locator files (Streets and names of owners) (Box 1323A)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 1324)
        - 61-142 (Box 1325)
      - Flat files
        - 35, (39, 62, 63), 44, 59, 61 (Box 1326)
        - 111, 122, 139 (Box 1327)
    - Beacon Falls abstracts of title (Box 1328)
    - Bethany
      - Atlas for locations in Bethany (also for locations in Prospect and Woodbridge) (Box 1329)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets (A-Z) (Box 1329A)
        - Names of owners (A-Z) (Box 1329B)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 1330)
        - 61-105 (Box 1331)
        - 106-150 (Box 1332)
        - 151-210 (Box 1333)
        - 211-300 (Box 1334)
        - 301-370 (Box 1335)
        - 371-462 (Box 1336)
        - 463-540 (Box 1337)
        - 541-680 (Box 1338)
        - 681-775 (Box 1339)
        - 776-792 (Box 1340)
      - Flat files
        - 48, 53, 71 (Box 1341)
        - 76, 218, 306, 457 (Box 1342)
        - 460, 548, 566, 608, 615, 662, 679, 687, 742 (Box 1343)
    - Branford
      See also: New Haven County Atlas, Box 1323 for New Haven County Atlas
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - Aceto Street - Harbor View Avenue (Box 1344)
          - Harbor Village -Pepperwood Lane (Box 1345)
          - Pequot Avenue - Zuwalick Lane (Box 1346)
        - Names of owners
          - A-F (Box 1347)
          - G-O (Box 1348)
          - P-Z (Box 1349)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 1350)
        - 61-124 (Box 1351)
        - 125-185 (Box 1352)
        - 186-245 (Box 1353)
        - 246-304 (Box 1354)
        - 305-375 (Box 1355)
        - 376-425 (Box 1356)
        - 426-480 (Box 1357)
        - 481-559 (Box 1358)
        - 560-635 (Box 1359)
        - 636-719 (Box 1360)
        - 720-810 (Box 1361)
        - 811-890 (Box 1362)
        - 891-979 (Box 1363)
        - 980-1055 (Box 1364)
        - 1056-1124 (Box 1365)
        - 1125-1199 (Box 1366)
        - 1200-1280 (Box 1367)
        - 1281-1374 (Box 1368)
        - 1375-1452 (Box 1369)
        - 1453-1520 (Box 1370)
        - 1521-1614 (Box 1371)
        - 1615-1680 (Box 1372)
        - 1681-1769 (Box 1373)
        - 1770-1850 (Box 1374)
        - 1851-1944 (Box 1375)
        - 1945-2018 (Box 1376)
        - 2019-2096 (Box 1377)
        - 2097-2158 (Box 1378)
        - 2159-2216 (Box 1379)
        - 2217-2270 (Box 1380)
        - 2271-2325 (Box 1381)
        - 2326-2392 (Box 1382)
        - 2393-2443 (Box 1383)
      - Flat files
        - Unnumbered, 4 (Box 1384)
        - 44 (Box 1385)
        - 75, 120, 122-124 (Box 1386)
        - 128, 140, 155, 162, 170, 296 (Box 1387)
        - 312, 328, 335, 391 (Box 1388)
        - 406, 460, 505, 526 (Box 1389)
        - 533, 550, 551, 599, 648, 661, 677, 694-695 (Box 1390)
        - 701, 762, 774, 836, 847, 862, 1139, 1142, 1256 (Box 1391)
        - 1279, 1296, 1311, 1361, 1380, 1384 (Box 1392)
        - 1415, 1422, 1474, 1488, 1500-1501 (Box 1393)
        - 1504, 1541, (1553, 1668), 1553 Supplemental (Box 1394)
        - 1553 Supplemental, (1586-1589), (1623, 2051), 1644, 1697, 1703, (364, 365, 1712) (Box 1395)
        - 1743, 1799, 1866 (Box 1396)
        - 1880, 1945, 1967, 2041, 2113, 2115 (Box 1397)
        - 2191, 2218, 2219 (Box 1398)
        - 2275, 2362, 2371, 2379, 2388, 2392 (Box 1399)
        - 2411 (Box 1400)
    - Bridgeport abstracts of title (Box 1401)
    - Bristol flat files (Box 1402)
    - Burlington abstract of title (Box 1402)
    - Cheshire
      - Atlas for street locations (Box 1403)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - A-M (Box 1404)
          - N-Z (Box 1405)
        - Names of owners
          - A-G (Box 1405)
          - H-Z (Box 1406)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-50 (Box 1407)
        - 51-120 (Box 1408)
        - 121-185 (Box 1409)
        - 186-245 (Box 1410)
        - 246-300 (Box 1411)
        - 301-370 (Box 1412)
        - 371-500 (Box 1413)
        - 501-620 (Box 1414)
        - 621-670 (Box 1415)
        - 721-860 (Box 1416)
        - 861-990 (Box 1417)
        - 991-1100 (Box 1418)
        - 1101-1225 (Box 1419)
        - 1226-1300 (Box 1420)
        - 1301-1406 (Box 1421)
      - Flat files
        - 9, 18, 40, 42, 50, 90, 95, 97 (Box 1422)
        - 105, 125, 206, 209, 237, 285, 300, 303, 313 (Box 1423)
        - 323, 361, 363, 368 (Box 1424)
        - 389, 395, 398, 409, 435, 564, 696, 729, 759 (Box 1425)
        - 786, 789, 791, 828, 867, 871, 876, 885, 886, 889, 906, 1024, 1064, 1073 (Box 1426)
        - 1079, 1100, 1145, 1148, 1156, 1175 (Box 1427)
        - 1189, 1206, 1208, 1236 (Box 1428)
        - 1237, 1314, 1316 (Box 1429)
    - Clinton
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets (Box 1430)
        - Names of owners (Box 1430)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 1431)
        - 61-109 (Box 1432)
        - 110-175 (Box 1433)
        - 176-250 (Box 1434)
        - 251-331 (Box 1435)
      - Flat files
        - Unnumbered, 2, 14-15, 44, 50-52, 84-86 (Box 1436)
        - 87 and Killingworth 30, 101, 262, 276, 302, 305 (Box 1437)
    - Coventry abstract of title (Box 1438)
    - Cromwell
      - Abstract of title (Box 1438)
      - Flat files (Box 1438)
    - Danbury abstracts of title (Box 1439)
    - Darien abstracts of title (Box 1439)
    - Deep River abstracts of title (Box 1439)
    - Derby
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-83 (Box 1440)
        - 84-133 (Box 1441)
      - Flat files
      - 13-15, 40-41, 43, 56, 58, 65 (Box 1442)
      - 67-81, 91, 92, 100, 109, 119-121 (Box 1443)
    - Durham
      - Atlas (Key for locations) (Box 1443A)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-68 (Box 1444)
        - 70-120 (Box 1445)
      - Flat files
        - 7, 9-10, 16, 18, 20-22 (Box 1446)
        - 44, 60, 69, 82, 90, 93, 111-112 (Box 1447)
    - East Haddam abstracts of title (Box 1448)
    - East Hartford abstract of title (Box 1448)
    - East Haven
      - Atlases (two tax assessment maps), Circa 1977 and 1980 (Box 1448A)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - Admiral Street - Clark Avenue (Box 1449)
          - Clearview Avenue - Fisco Drive (Box 1450)
          - Fiume Street - Hellstorm Road (Box 1451)
          - Hemingway Avenue - Laura Lane (Box 1452)
          - Laurel Street - Myrtle Avenue (Box 1453)
          - Naugatuck Street - Russo Avenue (Box 1454)
          - Street Andrew Avenue - Thompson Street (Box 1455)
          - Thornton Drive - Zolan Drive (Box 1456)
        - Names of owners
          - Ables - Fleetwood (Box 1456A)
          - Flint - Lang (Box 1456B)
          - Langrock - Provost (Box 1456C)
          - Quillan - Tipping (Box 1456D)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-55 (Box 1457)
        - 56-109 (Box 1458)
        - 110-175 (Box 1459)
        - 176-220 (Box 1460)
        - 221-307 (Box 1461)
        - 308-380 (Box 1462)
        - 381-460 (Box 1463)
        - 461-560 (Box 1464)
        - 561-650 (Box 1465)
        - 651-735 (Box 1466)
        - 736-825 (Box 1467)
        - 826-930 (Box 1468)
        - 931-1020 (Box 1469)
        - 1021-1110 (Box 1470)
        - 1111-1200 (Box 1471)
        - 1201-1320 (Box 1472)
        - 1321-1420 (Box 1473)
        - 1421-1520 (Box 1474)
        - 1521-1610 (Box 1475)
        - 1611-1700 (Box 1476)
        - 1701-1810 (Box 1477)
        - 1811-1916 (Box 1478)
        - 1917-2020 (Box 1479)
        - 2021-2140 (Box 1480)
        - 2141-2240 (Box 1481)
        - 2241-2350 (Box 1482)
        - 2351-2478 (Box 1483)
        - 2479-2600 (Box 1484)
        - 2601-2731 (Box 1485)
        - 2732-2849 (Box 1486)
        - 2850-2964 (Box 1487)
        - 2965-3084 (Box 1488)
        - 3085-3179 (Box 1489)
        - 3180-3278 (Box 1490)
        - 3279-3410 (Box 1491)
        - 3411-3520 (Box 1492)
        - 3521-3636 (Box 1493)
        - 3637-3787 (Box 1494)
        - 3788-3920 (Box 1495)
        - 3921-4040 (Box 1496)
        - 4041-4140 (Box 1497)
        - 4141-4230 (Box 1498)
        - 4231-4294 (Box 1498A)
      - Flat files
        - 42, 114, 115, 222, 296, 399, 435 (Box 1499)
        - 485, 613 (Box 1500)
        - 661, 676, 679, 690 (Box 1501)
        - 695, 711 (Box 1502)
        - 718, 809, 1099, 1374, 1527, 1619, 1661 (Box 1503)
        - 1781, 2012, 2059, 2153, 2283, 2322 (Box 1504)
        - 2351, 2514, 2575, 2576, 2623, 2642, 2681, 2716, 2828, 2880 (Box 1505)
        - 2912, 2920, 3048, 3063 (Box 1506)
        - 3186, 3187, 3188, 3191, 3220, 3227, 3417, 3424 (Box 1507)
        - 3856, 3868 (Box 1508)
        - 4017, 4103, 4117, 4156 (Box 1509)
    - East Lyme abstracts of title (Box 1510)
    - Easton abstract of title (Box 1510)
    - Enfield abstract of title (Box 1510)
    - Essex
      - Abstract of title (Box 1510)
      - Flat files (Box 1511)
    - Fairfield
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1511)
      - Flat file (Box 1511)
    - Greenwich abstracts of title (Box 1511)
    - Groton
      - Abstracts of title (Box 1512)
      - Flat files (Box 1513)
    - Guilford
      - Atlas (Key for locations) (Box 1514)
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - A-N (Box 1515)
          - O-Z (Box 1516)
        - Names of owners
          - A-C (Box 1516)
          - D-Z (Box 1517)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-97 (Box 1518)
        - 98-174 (Box 1519)
        - 175-250 (Box 1520)
        - 251-326 (Box 1521)
        - 327-405 (Box 1522)
        - 406-460 (Box 1523)
        - 461-530 (Box 1524)
        - 531-595 (Box 1525)
        - 596-640 (Box 1526)
        - 641-706 (Box 1527)
        - 707-763 (Box 1528)
        - 764-838 (Box 1529)
        - 839-935 (Box 1530)
        - 936-1069 (Box 1531)
        - 1070-1172 (Box 1532)
        - 1173-1275 (Box 1533)
        - 1276-1350 (Box 1534)
        - 1351-1405 (Box 1535)
      - Flat files
        - 6, 8 (Box 1536)
        - 39, 48 (Box 1537)
        - 44-47, 49-52, 84, 87, 94, 156, 160, 169 (Box 1538)
        - 206, 311, 317, 332, 340, 373, 406, 414-415, 427, 469 (Box 1539)
        - 533, 543, 573, 578, 665, 784, 800, 811, 826, 842 (Box 1540)
        - 853, 875, 932, 975, 1018, 1031, 1032 (Box 1541)
        - 1064, 1078, 1096, 1163, 1180, 1183, 1209 (Box 1542)
        - 1260, 1315, 1319, 1324, 1373, 1401 (Box 1543)
    - Hamden
      - Index card locator files
        - Streets
          - Abby Lane - Blue Hills Avenue (Box 1544)
          - Blue Hills Drive - Claire Terrace (Box 1545)
          - Clark Street - Dixwell Avenue (Box 1546)
          - Doran Avenue - Foch Street (Box 1547)
          - Foote Street - Hartford Tpke. (Box 1548)
          - Haverford Street - Kelly Road (Box 1549)
          - Kildeer Road - Merritt Street (Box 1550)
          - Michael Road - Paramount Avenue (Box 1551)
          - Park Avenue - Rockview Road (Box 1552)
          - Rockwood Road - Stanley Road (Box 1553)
          - State Street - Waite Street (Box 1554)
          - Wakefield Street - Whitney Avenue street addresses to 2000 (Box 1555)
          - Whitney Avenue street addresses above 2000 - York Hill Road (Box 1556)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 1557)
        - 61-110 (Box 1558)
        - 111-180 (Box 1559)
        - 181-250 (Box 1560)
        - 251-286 (Box 1561)
        - 287-360 (Box 1562)
        - 361-435 (Box 1563)
        - 436-510 (Box 1564)
        - 511-585 (Box 1565)
        - 586-675 (Box 1566)
        - 676-765 (Box 1567)
        - 766-850 (Box 1568)
        - 851-930 (Box 1569)
        - 931-1035 (Box 1570)
        - 1036-1115 (Box 1571)
        - 1116-1210 (Box 1572)
        - 1211-1300 (Box 1573)
        - 1301-1390 (Box 1574)
        - 1391-1493 (Box 1575)
        - 1494-1610 (Box 1576)
        - 1611-1703 (Box 1577)
        - 1704-1795 (Box 1578)
        - 1796-1880 (Box 1579)
        - 1881-1976 (Box 1580)
        - 1977-2072 (Box 1581)
        - 2073-2165 (Box 1582)
        - 2166-2240 (Box 1583)
        - 2241-2330 (Box 1584)
        - 2331-2416 (Box 1585)
        - 2417-2518 (Box 1586)
        - 2519-2612 (Box 1587)
        - 2613-2700 (Box 1588)
        - 2701-2789 (Box 1589)
        - 2790-2875 (Box 1590)
        - 2876-2984 (Box 1591)
        - 2985-3072 (Box 1592)
        - 3073-3160 (Box 1593)
        - 3161-3250 (Box 1594)
        - 3251-3355 (Box 1595)
        - 3356-3450 (Box 1596)
        - 3451-3555 (Box 1597)
        - 3556-3640 (Box 1598)
        - 3641-3715 (Box 1599)
        - 3716-3800 (Box 1600)
        - 3801-3890 (Box 1601)
        - 3891-3985 (Box 1602)
        - 3986-4069 (Box 1603)
        - 4070-4175 (Box 1604)
        - 4176-4250 (Box 1605)
        - 4251-4344 (Box 1606)
        - 4345-4440 (Box 1607)
        - 4441-4549 (Box 1608)
        - 4550-4645 (Box 1609)
        - 4646-4760 (Box 1610)
        - 4761-4845 (Box 1611)
        - 4846-4930 (Box 1612)
        - 4931-5031 (Box 1613)
        - 5032-5125 (Box 1614)
        - 5126-5220 (Box 1615)
        - 5221-5348 (Box 1616)
        - 5349-5455 (Box 1617)
        - 5456-5610 (Box 1618)
        - 5611-5760 (Box 1619)
        - 5761-5880 (Box 1620)
        - 5881-6004 (Box 1621)
        - 6005-6150 (Box 1622)
        - 6151-6270 (Box 1623)
        - 6271-6405 (Box 1624)
        - 6406-6530 (Box 1625)
        - 6531-6625 (Box 1626)
        - 6626-6770 (Box 1627)
        - 6771-6890 (Box 1628)
        - 6891-7020 (Box 1629)
        - 7021-7140 (Box 1630)
        - 7141-7280 (Box 1631)
        - 7281-7395 (Box 1632)
        - 7396-7540 (Box 1633)
        - 7541-7660 (Box 1634)
        - 7661-7787 (Box 1635)
        - 7788-7905 (Box 1636)
        - 7906-8030 (Box 1637)
        - 8031-8170 (Box 1638)
        - 8171-8317 (Box 1639)
        - 8318-8470 (Box 1640)
        - 8471-8600 (Box 1641)
        - 8601-8727 (Box 1642)
        - 8728-8860 (Box 1643)
        - 8861-9005 (Box 1644)
        - 9006-9135 (Box 1645)
        - 9136-9240 (Box 1646)
        - 9241-9350 (Box 1647)
        - 9351-9480 (Box 1648)
        - 9481-9600 (Box 1649)
        - 9601-9715 (Box 1650)
        - 9716-9815 (Box 1651)
        - 9816-9950 (Box 1652)
        - 9951-10055 (Box 1653)
        - 10056-10160 (Box 1654)
        - 10161-10270 (Box 1655)
        - 10271-10375 (Box 1656)
        - 10376-10480 (Box 1657)
        - 10481-10528 (Box 1658)
    - Flat files (Numerical)
      - 30, 44, 51, 100, 171, 245 (Box 1659)
      - 280, 304, 320, 403, 462, 488, 652 (Box 1660)
      - 711, 771, 773, 864, 959, 1006 (Box 1661)
      - 1119, 1148, 1189, 1363 (Box 1662)